How do you get rid of Hamas if you don't do it the way Israel is currently doing it, albeit...
You do what America did with the Osama bin Laden raid.
We didn't go drop a nuke on Pakistan.
We didn't go destroy 6,000 residential buildings in the middle of Pakistan.
We sent in special forces.
Is it more dangerous to the special forces?
Of course! That's the point of special forces.
Try to find the hostages.
Does it look like Israel's trying to find the hostages?
If I have a family member that's a hostage, I'm disgusted by what Netanyahu's doing now.
How do you know they're not in the buildings you're dropping bombs on?
How do you know they're not in the tunnels you're dropping bombs on?
How do you know they're not in the hospitals you're dropping bombs on?
So if you want the hostages rescued, every rational human being can agree this is not the way to do it.
This is the way to do death and destruction for the sake of death and destruction.
It's collective punishment.
It's genocide against Palestinians.
And the world has to speak out.
So my way is not pleasant either.
It involves a lot of folks dying on both sides.
I understand that.
Those are super hard choices.
But go find Hamas.
Go find the hostages.
Go rescue them.
Instead of wantingly, indiscriminately, killing after killing.
And let's be honest, when you drop a bomb and a kid's head explodes and a grandmother is incinerated, that is terrorism.
Killing three.